starstyle.com 2006-08-12

# StarStyle - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Last Updated December 27, 2005 

Starstyle.com respects the privacy of its users and we recognize that we must maintain and use customer information responsibly. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect on our website and how we use such information; please read it carefully. Your use of our website indicates to us that you have read and accepted our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

*  When you visit the Starstyle.com, our software automatically collects usage information. Website usage information is anonymous information that describes how our users navigate through our website, and it includes the number and frequency of user to each web page and the length of their stays. We collect anonymous information automatically sent to us by web browsers, such as browser type, referrer data that identifies the web page visited prior and subsequent to visiting our Starstyle.com, and IP address. An IP address is an identifier that is assigned to every computer or network when accessing the Internet. Every time a visitor requests a page from our website, our software log the visitor’s IP address. We may collect IP addresses for a variety of purposes, such as system administration, to report aggregate information to our business partners or to audit the number of visits to different pages on our website. 

*  Starstyle.com receives and stores certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. Like most websites, we use "cookies," and obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses our pages. Cookies are anonymous information files that websites may place on your computer to provide extended functionality and to personalize experience. We may use cookies for a number of purposes. For example, we may use cookies to track usage patterns on the website and we may use cookies when we conduct polls and sweepstakes to limit multiple responses and registrations. We do not store any personal information in cookies, but we may link the cookie to any information we collect. You can, of course, disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of the website will not operate correctly if you disable cookies. You should consult with your browser’s provider/manufacturer if you have any questions regarding disabling cookies. 

*  We only collect personal information such as your name, email, and address, which you provide to us when you participate in a sweepstakes, promotion, or send us feedback. We also monitor site use and traffic patterns to improve our website design and the products and services we offer. 

*  Starstyle.com will not rent or sell your personal information (including email address) for any purpose. Starstyle.com will only share personal information you provide to us when participating in sweepstakes with partner companies if you allow us to do so. 

*  If you are under the age of 13, you are not permitted to submit any personal information to Starstyle.com. Starstyle.com is intended for users who are 13 years of age and older.  

*  Third Party Advertising: The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by DoubleClick, our Web advertising partner. Information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you. For more information about DoubleClick, cookies,and how to "opt-out", please click here: [ http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy)

*  Third Party Cookies: in the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. 

If you have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, you may contact us at [privacy@starstyle.com](mailto:privacy@starstyle.com).
